planet-9.com 2015-12-28

# Planet-9 Porsche Forum - Privacy Policy

CaymanClub.Net takes privacy and data protection issues seriously. We have designed this Privacy Policy to explain how we handle personally identifiable information collected from merchants who register for services and submit information to CaymanClub.Net through the Internet.

As the CaymanClub.Net services evolve, we may revise this policy, so please check back frequently. If you have questions about CaymanClub.Net privacy practices please contact us at [ webmaster@CaymanClub.Net](mailto:webmaster@caymanclub.net).

You will receive an autoresponse from us confirming that we have received your e-mail. If you do not receive an auto-response, please contact CaymanClub.Net Customer Support by phone or chat.

**Scope of this Privacy Policy**

This Privacy Policy covers CaymanClub.Net’s treatment of personally identifiable information collected from members (hereafter “members” or “you”) who use the CaymanClub.Net website services, as well as consumer information that we acquire in the course of our business. This Policy also covers the treatment of personally identifiable information that CaymanClub.Net’s business partners may share with it.

This Policy does not apply to the practices of companies that CaymanClub.Net does not own or control, or to people that CaymanClub.Net does not employ or manage.

**Information Collection and Use**

CaymanClub.Net collects personally identifiable information when you register for an CaymanClub.Net account, and when you use certain CaymanClub.Net products and services. CaymanClub.Net may also receive personally identifiable information from its resellers and other business partners.

When you register with CaymanClub.Net, we ask for your contact information (such as your name, street address and email address), as well as certain information pertaining to your car if you own the model represented on this site.

In the course of processing a payment transaction, we typically receive from the merchant or a financial institution information related to the transaction. This normally includes information about the payment that a consumer has furnished the merchant or financial institution in placing the order. We do not acquire any information directly from consumers through the [www.CaymanClub.Net](http://www.authorize.net/) Web site.

The personally identifiable information we acquire in processing payment transactions varies according to the nature of the transaction and the way in which merchants or financial institutions are using our payment services. It may include, for example, the amount of the transaction, the consumer’s name, credit card number and expiration date, checking account number, billing address, and shipping address.

CaymanClub.Net uses the information collected to fulfill your requests for certain products and services, to process payment transactions, to facilitate billing, and otherwise deliver the payment gateway services. We may also send merchants service announcements, newsletters, and periodic notices about specials, new products and services and products and services offered by CaymanClub.Net business partners. Personally identifiable consumer information is used to process payment transactions and for no other purpose.

CaymanClub.Net does not offer services or sell products to children. CaymanClub.Net does not request or knowingly collect personally identifiable contact information from anyone under the age of 13.

**Information Sharing and Disclosure**

Protecting personally identifiable information about merchants and consumers is an important part of our business. We share and disclose such information only as described below.

CaymanClub.Net sends personally identifiable information about you to other companies or people:: 1) when we have your consent to share the information; 2) when we need to share your information with third parties, such as banks and credit card processors, to provide the product or service you have requested; 3) in connection with products and services offered by CaymanClub.Net business partners and/or companies who work on behalf of CaymanClub.Net to provide a product or service to you; 4) it is appropriate to comply with law; 5) it is necessary to enforce or apply the terms and conditions of our Member Agreement and other applicable agreements; or 6) it is necessary to protect the rights, property, or safety of CaymanClub.Net, our users, or others, which may include the exchange of information with other organizations for fraud protection and/or risk reduction.  
In the event that CaymanClub.Net is acquired, merchant account information may be one of the transferred assets. 

**Information Security**

Information security is critical to our business. We work to protect the security of your information during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts information you input. We store information gathered on secure computers located in a locked data center. The number of employees involved in the management of the data center that have physical access to these computers is limited. We use firewalls and other security technology to prevent our computers from being accessed by unauthorized persons.

We also require that any personally identifiable consumer information sent to us by you be encrypted using SSL encryption. To learn more about SSL, go to: [ http://webopedia.internet.com/TERM/S/SSL.html](http://webopedia.internet.com/TERM/S/SSL.html).

It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your Login ID/password and to your computer. Be sure to sign off when finished using a shared computer and otherwise protect the password used to access the CaymanClub.Net services.

**Account Information and Preferences**

CaymanClub.Net gives you the ability to edit your CaymanClub.Net Account Information and preferences at any time, including whether you want CaymanClub.Net to contact you about specials and new products, by using the **Edit Your Details** option in your User Control Panel (UserCP) or the **Customize Profile** option. (see the CaymanClub.Net User Guide FAQ for more details), or by emailing us at [ webmaster@caymanclub.net](mailto:webmaster@caymanclub.net)

**Notice for European Users**

CaymanClub.Net is located in the United States. Any information that you provide to CaymanClub.Net will be transferred out of the EU to the United States. By providing personal information to us, you are consenting to its storage and use as described herein.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

CaymanClub.Net reserves the right to modify or amend this Privacy Policy at any time and for any reason. If there are material changes to this statement or in how CaymanClub.Net will use personally identifiable information, CaymanClub.Net will post notice on the CaymanClub.Net homepage at [www.CaymanClub.Net](http://www.authorize.net/) prior to implementing the change. The amended Terms shall automatically become effective immediately after they are posted. Your continued use of the site or CaymanClub.Net services after the posting of the amended Terms on the Site constitutes your affirmative: (a) acknowledgement of the terms and its modifications; and (b) agreement to abide and be bound by the terms, as amended. If you have additional questions about this Policy, please contact us at [ webmaster@caymanclub.net](mailto:webmaster@caymanclub.net)
